https://awcaonline.com/privacy-policy/

Pin0
Privacy PolicyAWCAOnline.com collects and uses personal data as needed in order for us to provide you with services and products purchased, subscribed to or supported (collectively, our "Services"). Your personal data includes information such as:NameMailing address, city, state, zip codeEmail addressPhone numberOther data that could directly or indirectly identify you in order to provide support as requested by youOur Privacy Policy will explain to you what data we collect, and how we use your personal data. It also describes how you can access, update, or otherwise take control of the personal data that we have collected from you.what data is collected?Most of your personal data is collected from you when:You enroll in our Distance Learning Program;You purchase an eBook;You request assistance from our customer support team;You complete surveys, subscribe to newsletters, or request other information from us.In order to deliver the best Services to you, we may collect the following information:Service Usage Data is automatically collected when you interact with our Services. This information may include data about your interactions with the features, content and links contained in our Services, time of interaction, browser type and configuration, operating system used, IP address, language preferences, and other cookie data. While none of this data will allow us to directly identify who you are, some of this data can be used to approximate your location. This is solely to allow us to know where our audience is and how our products and services can be altered to more closely meet the needs of that audience.Supplementary Data may be received about you from third party sources, such as public databases, but the AWCA will never release information of any kind about you to anyone. We do not sell, rent, lease or knowingly make any of your information available to anyone for any reason.how do we use your data?We believe in minimizing the data we collect. We will only use your data when we have been given permission to do so, when it is needed to deliver the Services that you have purchased, or for legal compliance or other lawful purposes. These usages include:Delivering, updating, and improving the Services that we provide to you. We collect various data relating to your purchase, use, and interactions with our Services. We use this data to.Improve and optimize the performance of our Services,Identify and investigate security risks, errors, problems, and needed enhancements to our Services,Detect and prevent fraud and abuse of our Services,Collect statistics about the use of our Services,Analyze how you use our Services and which of our Services are most relevant to you, andMost of the data that we collect is statistical data about how people use our Services and is not linked to any personal data.Sharing with the secured PayPal payment network. This may include:Delivering content and communications to you (such as email or a product or service your purchased or subscribed to),Analyzing Service usage and customer demographics,Managing customer relationships, andAt no time does the AWCA have access to your PayPal account or any financial information regarding you or your account.how is your data stored and protected?We follow generally accepted standards to collect, store and protect personal data, including the use of encryption. We retain personal data for as long as it is needed to provide the Services you have requested, and thereafter for legal and business purposes. These may include retention periods:Mandated by legal, contractual, or similar obligations;For resolving, preserving, enforcing or defending our legal and contractual rights;Needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.how can you accesS, update and/or delete your data?You can access, view and update your personal data by signing into your account and visiting "My Account". If you are unable to access "My Account" for any reason, you may contact us as described in the "Contact Us" section below.If you make a request to delete your personal data, that request will be honored only to the extent where the data is no longer needed for the Services you have purchased, or when it is no longer required for our business, legal or contractual record keeping requirements.Age restrictionsOur Services are only available for purchase for those who are over the age of 18. Our Services are not designed to target, entice, or be consumed by individuals under the age of 18. If you know of or have reason to believe someone under the age of 18 has provided us with any personal data, please contact us.changes to our privacy policyWe reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Please review this document from time to time so that you are aware of what information we collect and how we use it.contact usIf you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending an email via our Contact Us form.
ABOUT USSince 1993, the AWCA has been producing exceptional members at our private gym, as well as providing innovative Wing Tsun training media to all levels of practitioners.OUR CLASSESWing TsunEscrimaRESOURCESForms, Drills & ApplicationseBook Training SeriesDistance Learning ProgramYouTube ChannelFacebook ChannelSOCIAL MEDIA SHARING
Share0
Tweet0
Share0
Pin0
© 2020 Arizona Wing Chun Association. All rights reserved.Home | Site Map | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer | Contact Us
